Hello, I'm Nogizaka46 and I'd like to introduce myself. We, Nogizaka46, are currently holding auditions for the 6th term students.
We are here at Honjo Daiichi High School.
We would like to put up the posters here.
It's a surprise.
I'm so nervous. I wonder if they will be okay?
I wonder if I'll be okay. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to enjoy putting up posters with everyone.
I'm off!
It looks like a school.
There are so many things on display.
Kigawaga.
Ah!
Don't believe it. Beware of sweet words.
It's cool.
It's really cool.
Let's take a look inside.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Wow, look at those shoes.
We're a school for slippers.
Isn't that what it's all about?
We used to go to school everywhere with slippers.
Is that so?
It's not so easy to find a street like this.
I used to change my shoes.
I always wanted to be a shoe-changer.
What kind of things?
I heard there's tobacco.
Look.
It's amazing. Baseball.
Is it a strong baseball school too?
Yes. They've won a lot of championships.
What? It's cute.
What kind of uniform was it?
It's all in my tongue.
You don't have a tongue.
So, the sweater is Mizue.
Yes, indeed.
Isn't it stylish? It's amazing.
It's so neat.
I like the green.
It's cute.
It's a school.
Stylish.
Well then, since it looks like everyone is still waiting for 10 seconds
I'd like to go to the sisters.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
I'm getting a little tired.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Club members
I'm not taking my shoes off.
Oh, no, no, no, no, I see them.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
Thank you for watching.
Hello.
This is Nogizaka46.
Um...
Oh, is that you?
Are you Mr. Arai-kun by any chance?
That's Mr. Arai-kun.
Actually, Mr. Arai-kun, he's the one who's currently holding the audition for
Nogizaka46 is holding an audition
I'm holding an audition,
and I was applying for a place to put up a poster.
where to put up the posters,
Arai-kun..,
He applied for it and came to put it up,
He came to put up the posters.
Thank you very much.
After joining Nogizaka,
I have learned so many things about Nogizaka that I didn't know about myself,
I have learned so many things
I have learned a lot of things that I didn't know before,
I have learned a lot of things that I didn't know
I am looking forward to the future,
I encourage you to have the courage to take the first step,
We hope that we can give you the courage to take the first step,
We hope that we can help you to take a step forward
We hope that we can help you to take the first step forward,
Some of you may not be confident
but we are here to help you,
We hope you will take the first step and apply,
I would be very happy if you could take a step forward and apply.
I would be very happy if you could take the first step and apply.
Is this the 4th class of the 1st year?
Actually, I was in
I was in the 4th grade of the 1st year,
I was in the first year of high school,
during the summer vacation.
I applied for the job,
I was able to become a member of Nogizaka46
I was really excited to be a member of Nogizaka46.
I really did at that time,
summer vacation,
I didn't have much to do,
I didn't really have anything worthwhile to do,
I was always
I always feel like I have nothing to do,
I don't have anything that I can be passionate about when I go home,
I have something I can be passionate about when I go home, or something I can be passionate about at school,
I have something I can be passionate about,
I don't have anything that I'm passionate about.
I didn't have anything that I could be passionate about,
That's when I found this application form,
I found this application form and thought, "I want to be
I decided to apply for it,
If there are people who want to try something new as well, please let me know,
I would be very happy if you would take the first step,
I would be happy if someone who wants to try something new like me could take the first step.
It's cool, isn't it?
That's great.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
School.
I really miss it.
I miss it.
Arayukun, please.
I'm very happy to meet you
I'm so happy to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming, too.
Shall we do one shot apiece?
Let's go.
What's going on? Are you guys in a club or something?
Oh!
He's so cute.
So cute.
It's like school.
It's so school.
It's like the girl I'm about to confess my feelings to.
That's for sure.
Dan Valley Club.
Are you involved in any clubs?
What club?
Dance club.
Dance club?
You dance?
I see you have a lot of different clubs.
It's perfect.
Dancing.
If you're an idol, you'll need it.
I wish I'd learned to dance.
I think so too.
Wow, it's like school.
I miss it.
You had class this morning too?
I see.
Good work.
Thanks for coming.
Maybe I'll ask him something at Nogizaka.
I'll ask him.
Is there someone like a tightrope?
Sis.
Really?
With your sister?
I don't know if I've ever met anyone like that.
He's a very nice man.
Me and...
With Iyoki.
By the way...
Sakura Endo
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I'm very happy. Very happy.
Oh, what a surprise.
What a nice place.
What a nice place for a chat like this.
There is.
Are you okay? Is the mean balance okay?
Is it even?
Liver
Oh, it's hard.
Harder than expected?
Surprisingly hard.
But it's very nostalgic.
Nostalgic hardness.
There's a nostalgic hardness to this.
It's hard.
It's so hard.
Life is sticking out like a sieve.
It's okay. - It's okay.
Okay. - Okay.
It's clear.
Are we gonna be okay?
I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
So the poster is clear.
It's clear.
We did it!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you so much.
Oh my god!
So many people.
Thank you so much.
Yay!
We are still accepting applications for this contest.
I hope you will check it out!
You can apply until March 5th.
I hope everyone will think about it and think about it and think about it and apply until the last day.
I'll be waiting for you all!
I'm waiting for you all.
I'll be waiting for you.
We're waiting for you.
I'll be waiting.
We did it!
So we've finished putting up the posters!
We're done!
Bye, bye, bye.
Bye-bye!
Thank you very much.
Apply now!